The Friends of the Rockbridge Choral Society Papers WLU.Coll.0628
Washington and Lee University, University Library Special Collections and Archives
The Friends of the Rockbridge Choral Society Papers
1997-2014
Washington and Lee University, University Library Special Collections and Archives
WLU.Coll.0628
3 Box
1 Item One folder of large posters removed to oversize drawer 27
- Text Materials (Box 1, Folder 0-46)
  - Control (Box 1, Folder 0)
  - Programs, 1997-12-13-2001-03-13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 2001-03-25-2003-03-11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 2003-03-16-2004-12-05 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 2004-12-05-2007-03-18 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 2007-03-18-2009-04-05 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 2009-12-06-2010-12-04 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 2010-12-12-2011-12-03 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 2012-04-22-2013-12-07 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 2014-01-12-2015-01-25 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 2015-01-25-2015-12-05 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter, 1999-2014 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lee Chapel Reservations, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Pledge List, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Treakle Foundation Grant, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dominion VA Power Grant, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society Fundraising, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society Budget, 1999-2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Ticket Sales, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Handel- Messiah- Concert Banner, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Creation Orchestra, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bach- B Minor Mass, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Christmas Concert, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society Roster, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Financial Documents, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Seasonal Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Seasonal Planning, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Dessert with the Director, 2010-04-14 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Friends Spring Fling, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Friends Financial Documents, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Friends- State Incorporation, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Friends List, 2000-11 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Friends Board Meeting, 2002-03 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Friends Thank You List, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Friends Thank You List, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Friends Treasurer's Report, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Friends Newsletter, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Friends Postage Stamp, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Friends- Various, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Friends- Various, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society- Various, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society- Various, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society- Various, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society- Various, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society- Various, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society- Various, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society- Various, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Photographs (Box 2, Folder 47-59)
  - Photographs, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Photographs, 2001-07-24-2001-12-02 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Photographs, 2001-12-25 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Photographs, 2002-03-25 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Photographs, 2002-04 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Photographs, 2002-12-25 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Photographs (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Photographs, 2003-2005-08 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Photographs, 2006-02-15-2006-08-13 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Photographs, 2007-02-25-2007-03-16 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Photographs, 2007-08-29-2011-12-25 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Photographs, Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Photographs, Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Mixed Materials (Box 3, Folder 60-69)
  - Photographs, Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Photographs, Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - January 2009 Concert and King David Version 1, 2009-01; 2010-04-11 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - King David Version 2 Copy 2, 2010-04-11 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - King David Version 2 Copy 2, 2010-04-11 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Posters, 2000-12-03-2005-12-10 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Posters, 2006-03-05-2009-04-05 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Posters, 2009-12-06-2013-04-06 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Posters, 2014-01-12-2015-12-05 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Rockbridge Choral Society, Miscellaneous and programs (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Large Posters, 2003-04-06-2010-01-17 (Box 3, Drawer 27)